Backstory so, a little backstory, where I grow up, there is a restaurant chain based on my hometown,
not going to mention it for privacy reasons, which was a pizzeria.
Like most pizzerias, they offered chicken wings, so this is where we cue the main story.
The most eventful night I had this year so one of my dad's co-workers, they worked for a company
which develops eye medical stuff in case you were wondering, bought in buffalo wings for lunch,
and he gave them to my dad for me. I could have had chicken nuggets or just normal chicken meat
to eat for dinner. At around, my dad picked me up from my grandpa's house, I do the cause both of
my parents work and they don't want to hire a babysitter, I noticed that he had a styrofoam
container with aluminium foil to preserve it, some of you can see where this is leading up to.
I waited for my dad to get in the car and asked him, me, dad, what is in that box from insert
pizzeria name, dad, it's buffalo wings where I grew up in, you were looked down upon if you
didn't like buffalo wings, so I was, of course, going to have them for dinner. It took about
minutes to head back to our house, irrelevant to the story, but my mum was there, and then my dad
took in the wings. So I got ready to microwave them. Before we go any further, let me just say
something. If you combine a microwave with aluminium foil, it will not end well. So,
me being the idiot year old I was, forgot to remove the foil, and then I heard my dad yell,
dad, don't start the microwave, I kept on walking like it didn't matter but in.
Seconds I put the amp together and ran like Sonic the Hedgehog to the microwave when I heard a spark.
My younger sister saw the spark and yelled at me to do something. Thankfully, it was only in there
for seconds, so it didn't cause much damage, except to the styrofoam container, a little hole
was punctured into it. I then had an adrenaline rush for minutes. Believe it or not, I didn't
get punished because my parents said I could learn from my mistakes, my parents weren't entitled,
to say the least. I told my friend about this minutes before finishing this post,
and his reactions made sense. TLDR, aluminium foil and microwaves can end you.